<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <title>Kesharose</title>
    <link href="http://kesharose.tk/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="http://kesharose.tk" />
    <updated>2018-10-18T18:49:44+07:00</updated>
    <author>
        <name>Sim Lian</name>
    </author>
    <id>http://kesharose.tk</id>

    <entry>
        <title>5 Tips to increase your company&#x27;s profit</title>
        <author>
            <name>Sim Lian</name>
        </author>
        <link href="http://kesharose.tk/5-tips-to-increase-your-companys-profit.html"/>
        <id>http://kesharose.tk/5-tips-to-increase-your-companys-profit.html</id>
            <category term="Business"/>

        <updated>2018-10-18T18:46:10+07:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="http://kesharose.tk/media/posts/1/" alt="" />
                    Now I'll show you tips on how to improve your company's cash. If you want your business to grow, you will have to work your target audience. This means knowing the customer who is willing to acquire your product or service, only so it is&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="http://kesharose.tk/media/posts/1/" alt="" />
                <p>Now I'll show you tips on how to improve your company's cash.</p>
<h2>1) Set your target audience</h2>
<p>If you want your business to grow, you will have to work your target audience. This means knowing the customer who is willing to acquire your product or service, only so it is feasible to achieve the goals outlined and even overcome them. </p>
<h2>2) have a differential</h2>
<p>Companies that have a market differential are much more likely to stand out and thus get more customers. As much as you trust your business, you need to have common sense and evaluate what you can deliver to your client beyond the quality of the product or service.<br><br>First ask yourself: Is my product really good? Would you as a customer buy it? What makes the public buy in my company and not my competitor? Make this assessment, and from there you can have new ideas to have something differentiated in the market and stand out from the competition, increasing your sales.</p>
<h2>3) Invest in technology</h2>
<p>It is extremely important to invest in technology to facilitate the analysis of results and from there have an assertive decision making.<br><br>As much as you like spreadsheets and even the notebook, it's practically impossible to get the profits to increase and make it grow if you don't invest in technology. It is an active reality in companies and, who does not accompany is outside, ends up losing space for competition.<br><br>A management system helps you integrate your business process and as a consequence it helps your business reduce costs and increase your profit margin.</p>
<h2>4) Reduce spending</h2>
<p>Decreasing spending helps improve the price of your product and make it more competitive with the market.<br><br>Review some plans that your company has adhered to and are not widely used as: an Internet plan with speed well above what is used or telephony. Also review the purchases for your stock, is being made too much purchases and the product is long stopped? We know that stationary stock is money stopped.<br><br>Analyze and leave your company with your real needs to have no negative impact at the end.</p>
<h2>5) Learn how to buy</h2>
<p>Selling is great, but practice alone doesn't guarantee profit. Knowing how to Buy is a differential for all companies that target profit.<br><br>Always look for suppliers that offer quality and cheaper price. Sometimes this does not become possible because suppliers also aim at profit. Therefore, buying products or services in large quantities will cause the supplier to have more attractive prices.<br><br>Well, these are some tips for you to apply and increase your company's profit margin. I hope I helped you to better see the benefits these actions can bring.<br><br>Continue tracking tips on how to leverage your business on our blog. One hug and the next! Source: <a href="http://calico-kids.com">http://calico-kids.com</a></p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
</feed>
